# Jonelle English

Tampa, FL | (813) 474-8062 | <u>jmenglish216@gmail.com</u> www.jonelleenglish.com

"Whatever you can do, or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it."

### **SUMMARY**

UX Designer from Tampa Bay with seven years of marketing and advertising skills. Certified Scrum Master (CSM and PSM I) and Professional Scrum Master with three years of experience working with development teams in Technology, Marketing, and Learning Experience Design. My career has transitioned into UX Design with ConnectWise. I am discovering user experience research, design, and frontend skills with this new role and with Bloc online since 2017. My passions are about combining user-centric insights, business goals, and human empathy through websites and applications.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**ConnectWise**, Tampa — *UX Designer* 

May 2018 - Present

Conduct user research

Design and prototype user interfaces and experiences

Test designs for validity through usability testing

Constantly communicate the performance of designs

Work closely with developers to ensure accuracy and consistency of product delivery

Maintain and uphold the ConnectWise Design System

## **Bisk Education**, Tampa — Certified Scrum Master

July 2015 - May 2018

Successfully guided ten development teams, consisting of 60 people, through the process of scrum and kanban in Technology, Marketing, and Learning Experience Design. Supported teams using a servant leadership style to create team-building opportunities and facilitate interpersonal conflict resolution. Developed Scrum/Kanban training with other Scrum Masters to provide education across departments.

# **Bisk Education**, Tampa — Marketing Operations Specialists

November 2013 - June 2015

Coordinating program launches in marketing for campaigns that included websites, landing pages, email, and print material. Managed the creation of project timelines and the delivery of assets between creative production teams and stakeholders. Projects such as, the New England College's rebranding of their website and all marketing content which won a Silver ADDY Award in 2016.

Link: https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/congratulations-bisk-education-silver-addy-joe-edwards/

## **INVEST Financial Corporation**, Tampa — Advertising Coordinator

April 2008 - November 2013

Managed the advertising submissions submitted for compliance review and assigned to the Advertising Review team. Our workload estimated about 1200 submissions per month.

### **EDUCATION**

#### Bloc

User Experience Design 2017-2018

Completed 500?+ hours on project-based online bootcamp studies.

Remote mentorship weekly to review and improve upon the progress.

Created user surveys, competitive analysis, and personas.

Defining the brand identity on projects: logo, fonts, colors, style guide.

Implemented user testing on sketches, wireframes, mockups, and clickable prototypes

Design tools include Adobe Illustrator, Sketch, Balsamiq, Invision, UsabilityHub, and UsterTesting.com

Coding projects in HTML, CSS, and Javascript

Dev tools include Atom and GitHub

# **University of South Florida**

B.A. in Psychology 2006-2008

### **SKILLS**

User Research

**User Stories** 

User Flows

Site Mapping

Competitive Analysis

UI Design

Prototyping

**Usability Testing** 

#### TOOLS

Figma

Invision

Sketch

Illustrator

HTML/CSS